UNTIL THE END OF THE WORLD
THE TRILOGY
PART ONE
Pietro,
You should be in bed.
I don't sleep anymore, doctor.
Speeping is "out".
- Shit!
- Yes...
- She didn't see us, Raymond.
- I'm sorry, we were not introduced.
- Claire Tourneur.
- I am Raymond, He's Chico.
Chico, you could apologize to...
Madame Tourneur.
- Are you all right?
- No, I'm not.
I'm sorry, I've been an idiot.
I'm sorry.
Will your car still work?
People always want to give definitions.
You say "Rock'n Roll"
they ask, "Which kind?".
But I just play rock'n roll.
I'm a drummer.
- Did you hear him playing?
- He's been breaking my head
for 15 years.
Raymond is the same. When he says
he is buddhist, people go crazy.
- They can't stand him!
- It's not the same.
There's nothing wrong in
being buddhist.
- In his job, yes.
- What's his job?
My job is...
fuck and fucking.
- I want a beer.
- For a change!
We might stop there.
Leave it there!
Don't touch it!
- Who's there?
- It's me.
I've got to talk with you.
Your bag's heavy.
- This is enough for being rich.
- You might pay a coffee in Rome.
Did you see well? It's 50,000!
What did I say?
It's the price for a cappuccino.
But with this one you could
buy half a cow in Ethiopia.
- Have you been there?
- Yes.
- Where else have you been?
- More or less everywhere.
I've never been anywhere.
I don't care.
- Well actually I've been in America.
- So, how much do you have there?
Count them, I leave it here.
Sleep on it.
Perfect!
I don't trust people
who do thing for free.
- And you'd be a buddhist?
- Realist!
So?
I agree, for 30%.
- We counted the money, we can find you.
- Calm down Raymond.
If you want to change your mind....
Do as you want.
If the address is not real,
we know where to find you.
It's not worth to try to fool us.
We don't know who will fetch the money.
If it's not me, and if
you want to contact me,
have a drink, listen to some music...
Yes! You never know.
This is my music.
It's just a demo.
Thanks, Chico.
- Don't lose time.
- Don't worry.
Here she is!
Where is she now ?
She should be between St. Etienne...
- and Lyon.
- still a long road.
- 15 more minutes?
- At least. Still has to dry up.
- You were lucky, and had good tyres.
- Hurry up!
Eugene speaking,
but I'm not here...
me neither.
Wait, I have to remove the foam.
- Will it hold til Paris?
- Yes, no problems.
But you're going to draw
people's attention with that foam.
I'm Trevor McPhee.
You saved my life.
Oh, it's you, Claire!
So you smoke now?
- Good morning.
Who is she? What is she doing here?
Uncle Anton, I have to...
On the contrary.
Are you escaping from the police?
Where is he from?
And you're... in honeymoon?
Excuse me.
Charly Yu.
OK.
It's for men!
- That way.
- Thank you!
- Miss! Wait!
- A foreigner?
There is a foreign woman.
Madam, are you sure you're not wrong?
This place is for men only!
It's no place for women here!
Only for men, forbidden to women.
Ehi, beautiful!
I need help.
- Winter ! No !
- Escape, run !
END OF PART ONE
UNTIL THE END OF THE WORLD